Tufts Observer UP055
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Observer, 1977 -- 1978; UP055.009; 1 Volumes; 27 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-01-20; UP055.009.009.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 9)
    [Admissions, Office of, 1978] Will use waiting list (includes photo).
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-01-27; UP055.009.009.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 33 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-02-03; UP055.009.009.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 32 Megabytes (Box 9)
    [Admissions] Applications increase. p. 3.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-02-10; UP055.009.009.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-02-17; UP055.009.009.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 43 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-02-24; UP055.009.009.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 39 Megabytes (Box 9)
    [Admissions] Applications increase (set record). pp. 1, 22.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-03-03; UP055.009.009.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 42 Megabytes (Box 9)
    [American association of University professors] Michaeolson report re sex bias favored; [Altered States of Consciousness Organization] May be final semester; [African-American Center] Co-Sponsors photography exhibition "The Transatlantic Rhythm", p. 11.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-03-09; UP055.009.009.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 30 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-03-24; UP055.009.009.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 30 Megabytes (Box 9)
    [Admissions] Wealth rarely considered. pp. 1, 16.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-03-31; UP055.009.009.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 28 Megabytes (Box 9)
    [Alexander, Kent] Elected Chairperson of 1978-79 TCU Senate. Tom Alperin Elected treasurer [to] TCU Senate pg. 52.
  - Observer, 1978-03-31; UP055.001182; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-04-07; UP055.009.009.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 46 Megabytes (Box 9)
    [Altered States of Consciousness Club] Novak speaks on marijuana use; [Afro-American Literature] Amiri Baraka gave lecture-discussion, p. 10; [Afro-American Society] Bobby Seale, co-founder and chairman of Black Panther Party, spoke to students at Afro-House, p. 19.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-04-14; UP055.009.009.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 42 Megabytes (Box 9)
    [Afro-American Society] Sponsors concerts, p. 5.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-04-21; UP055.009.009.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 49 Megabytes (Box 9)
    Alpha Sigma Phi.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-04-28; UP055.009.009.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 61 Megabytes (Box 9)
    [Alumni 1978] Share post-grad experiences, p. 5.
- Tufts Observer, 1978 -- 1979; UP055.010; 1 Volumes; 26 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of bound volumes of the Tufts Observer newspaper, dated from September 15, 1978 to May 17, 1979. In 1969, the Observer replaced the Tufts Weekly as the weekly student-published paper. Observer states that its objective is to be 'the newspaper of record' for Tufts University. The Observer covers current events and university news and sports. Typical features include editorials and opinion pieces, a calendar of events, art and culture articles, creative works, and comics.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-09-15; UP055.010.010.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 32 Megabytes (Box 10)
    [Admissions] Dean Behnke undershoots this year's class at 1134. p. 3.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-09-22; UP055.010.010.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 29 Megabytes (Box 10)
    [Alpha Tau Omega.] tax debt still in doubt. Administration 1978-1979. Tufts' Expansion. Nutrition Center given $21M; Mayer foresees expansion; Undergrad School; Plan commended.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-09-29; UP055.010.010.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 40 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Administration 1978-1979. Mayer's administrative change.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-10-06; UP055.010.010.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 31 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Administration 1978-1979. Tufts' Expansion. Debate over enrollment, undergrads.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-10-13; UP055.010.010.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 42 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Activities and Organizations, 1978-79. Car not needed with Tufts Mountain Club; [Ad Hoc committee on tenure and promotions] Forms tenure policy. P.3. Administration 1978-1979. Budgeting process altered in shake-up. Tufts' Expansion 1978-79. Harleston's report proposes new prgrams, facilities; Mayer clarifies enrollment plan; Impressive sight by Harleston.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-10-20; UP055.010.010.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 38 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Kent Alexander works with both sides; Senate calls for enrollment state; [American association of University professors] Panel discussions
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-10-27; UP055.010.010.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 48 Megabytes (Box 10)
    [Alumni awards committee] Alumni do more than raise money; [Alumni association] Alumni do more than raise funds; Sr. Michael Adas (Historian). Speaks on peasants. Administration 1978-1979. Mayer favors decreased enrollment.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-11-03; UP055.010.010.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 37 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Administration 1978-1979. Mayer's administrative change; Mayer ranked campus priorities. Kent Alexander breaks deadlock: TCU buffer funding.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-11-10; UP055.010.010.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 41 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-11-17; UP055.010.010.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 44 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-12-01; UP055.010.010.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 42 Megabytes (Box 10)
    [Admissions] Admissions office playing no small part in own popularity. p. 4. Students give resaons for choosing Tufts. p. 4. Deans release new admission estimate. pp. 1, 29. Student body keeps basic characterstics. p. 2. Reasons behind the Great Leap isolated. p.3. Effects of popularity jump: Fragile, handle with care. p. 3. Minority applications, enrollment up also. p. 3.
  - Tufts Observer, 1978-12-08; UP055.010.010.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 52 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-01-19; UP055.010.010.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 25 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-01-26; UP055.010.010.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 39 Megabytes (Box 10)
    [Advisory Committee on University Investments] Recommended that Tufts divest itself of holdings of US Corporations involved in Republic of S. Africa. pp. 1, 22. Committee applauds Apartheid decision. p. 16. Steven Weinstein says no to divestment. p. 20.
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-02-02; UP055.010.010.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 45 Megabytes (Box 10)
    [Admissions] Record numbers of applications expected. p. 3. Financial Committee takes request for buffer funding, p. 3.Administration 1978-1979. Administration seeks budget adjustments. Administrative shifts highlight Murnane.
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-02-09; UP055.010.010.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 49 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-02-16; UP055.010.010.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 36 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Administration 1979. Richard Landau, Director of Foundation resigns. Administration 1979. Tufts University Faculty questions Provost's resignation.
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-02-23; UP055.010.010.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 42 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-03-02; UP055.010.010.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 39 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-03-08; UP055.010.010.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 37 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-03-23; UP055.010.010.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 43 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-03-30; UP055.010.010.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 51 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-04-06; UP055.010.010.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 46 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-04-20; UP055.010.010.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 37 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-04-27; UP055.010.010.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 73 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-05-17; UP055.010.010.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 10)
- Tufts Observer, 1979 -- 1980; UP055.011; 1 Volumes; 26 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of bound volumes of the Tufts Observer newspaper, dated from September 6, 1979 to May 2, 1980. In 1969, the Observer replaced the Tufts Weekly as the weekly student-published paper. Observer states that its objective is to be 'the newspaper of record' for Tufts University. The Observer covers current events and university news and sports. Typical features include editorials and opinion pieces, a calendar of events, art and culture articles, creative works, and comics.
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-09-06; UP055.011.011.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Adminstration 1979. Administrators part of new hill look (photo article).
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-09-14; UP055.011.011.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 35 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-09-21; UP055.011.011.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 32 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-09-28; UP055.011.011.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 39 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-10-05; UP055.011.011.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 38 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-10-12; UP055.011.011.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-10-19; UP055.011.011.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 5 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-10-26; UP055.011.011.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 43 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-11-02; UP055.011.011.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 38 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-11-09; UP055.011.011.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 40 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-11-16; UP055.011.011.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 44 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Eric Aborjaily named codirector of film series. p. 3
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-11-30; UP055.011.011.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 39 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1979-12-07; UP055.011.011.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 44 Megabytes (Box 11)
    [American association of University professors] Cites drop in pay; ["All My Sons"] Adams crafts set design. ["All My Sons"] Review of Pen, Paint and Pretzels production (incl. photos).
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-01-25; UP055.011.011.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 44 Megabytes (Box 11)
    [Admisions, Office of, 1980] January entrances top 1979 figures.
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-02-01; UP055.011.011.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 44 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-02-08; UP055.011.011.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 48 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-02-15; UP055.011.011.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 44 Megabytes (Box 11)
    [African-American Center] Black culture featured, p. 11.
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-02-22; UP055.011.011.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 48 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-02-28; UP055.011.011.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 40 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-03-14; UP055.011.011.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 45 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-03-21; UP055.011.011.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 45 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Accouting Department set for overhaul. p. 23
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-03-28; UP055.011.011.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 55 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Chairman defends A-21 Task Force. p. 8-11. [Admisions, Office of, 1980] Applicant increase announced (includes photo).
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-04-11; UP055.011.011.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 39 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Kent Alexander (A 80) Winner of 1980 Wendell Phillips Memorial Scholarship (incl. photo); [American association of University professors] Testifies on CIA actions [includes photo]
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-04-18; UP055.011.011.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 35 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-04-25; UP055.011.011.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 42 Megabytes (Box 11)
    [Admisions, Office of, 1980] Kept busy during summer (includes photo). Admisions, Office of, 1980] Almost 3000 accepted for admission in September; [African-American Center] Collins, Pat resigns as director (includes photo), p. 3; [Agamemnon] Arena Theater finale, p. 9.
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-05-02; UP055.011.011.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 52 Megabytes (Box 11)
    [Agamemnon] Review of Arena Theater production (photo), p. 9; [Alumni council] Honors seniors
- Tufts Observer, 1980 -- 1981; UP055.012; 1 Volumes
  This series consists of bound volumes of the Tufts Observer newspaper, dated from September 5, 1980 to May 31, 1981. In 1969, the Observer replaced the Tufts Weekly as the weekly student-published paper. Observer states that its objective is to be 'the newspaper of record' for Tufts University. The Observer covers current events and university news and sports. Typical features include editorials and opinion pieces, a calendar of events, art and culture articles, creative works, and comics.
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-09-05; UP055.012.012.00001 (Box 12)
    Administration 1980-81. Editorial on new administrative trens. Administration 1980-81. New administration shifts toward streamlined management. (includes photo).
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-09-12; UP055.012.012.00002 (Box 12)
    [American association of University professors] Professor Winter chosen to head Tufts chapter AAUP; Administration 1980-81. Editorial on new administrative trens. [A-21 Task Force] Revamp goes smoothly. p.5, 23; Academic Structure and Governance, Committee on; Reviews academic structure; P.3.
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-09-19; UP055.012.012.00003 (Box 12)
    Administration 1980-81. Financial surplus figures.
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-09-26; UP055.012.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-10-03; UP055.012.012.00005 (Box 12)
    [Admissions, Office of, 1980-81] Director predicts decrease in enrollment.
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-10-10; UP055.012.012.00006 (Box 12)
    [Academic Honesty] Letter warning of illegal term paper sales at Tufts. p. 18
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-10-17; UP055.012.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-10-24; UP055.012.012.00008 (Box 12)
    [Admissions, Office of, 1980-81] Creates new image (includes photo).
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-10-31; UP055.012.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-11-07; UP055.012.012.00010 (Box 12)
    [Alumni/ae] Discuss successful jobs; [Admissions, Office of, 1980-81] University seeks diversity in admissions. Administration 1980-81. Three-year projection released (includes photo); [Afro-American Cultural Cente
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-11-14; UP055.012.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-11-21; UP055.012.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - Tufts Observer, 1980-12-05; UP055.012.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-01-30; UP055.012.012.00014 (Box 12)
    [A-21 Task Force] Tufts nears compliance. (includes photo) p. 5; [Administration] Nation awaiting decision on sex bias suit, p. 4; [Administration] Michael Hoffman resigns vice presidential post, p. 3, 25; [Afro-American Cultural Center] Harrell, Oscar W. appointed new director of African-American Center, p. 3; Editorial, p. 16. [Alcohol Abuse 1980-81] Students give mixed reactions to letter on alcohol (incl. photos). [Alcohol Abuse] Controversy over president's letter on alcohol.
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-02-06; UP055.012.012.00015 (Box 12)
    Administration 1980-81. Announces facilities planning evaluation (includes photo); [Afro-American Cultural Center] Silver Star Steel Band plays at Tufts, p. 7. [Alcohol Abuse 1980-1981] Editorial critical of survey on alcohol abuse.
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-02-13; UP055.012.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-02-20; UP055.012.012.00017 (Box 12)
    [Admissions, Office of, 1981] Applications exceed 10,000. (includes photo of dean)
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-02-27; UP055.012.012.00018 (Box 12)
    [Administration] Carton, Lonnie; Lonnie Carton loses bias case, p. 1, 25.
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-03-06; UP055.012.012.00019 (Box 12)
    [Administration] Firing reversed by court, p. 1, 23.
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-03-13; UP055.012.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-03-19; UP055.012.012.00021 (Box 12)
    [Alumni association] Senior award winners chosen; [American association of University students] Letter re: attendance of Tufts students at conference
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-04-03; UP055.012.012.00022 (Box 12)
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-04-10; UP055.012.012.00023 (Box 12)
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-04-14; UP055.012.012.00024 (Box 12)
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-04-24; UP055.012.012.00025 (Box 12)
    [Administration] Michael Hoffman proposes surplus-deficit policy, p. 3, 25. [Alumni 1981] Jumbo Club honors six alumni, p. 20.
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-05-01; UP055.012.012.00026 (Box 12)
    [Alcohol Abuse 1981] Awareness week comes to close (photo).
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-05-08; UP055.012.012.00027 (Box 12)
    [Administration] Top level changes. p. 5.
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-05-31; UP055.012.012.00028 (Box 12)
    [Administration] Sol Gittleman appointed new Provost; Steven Manos appointed new executive Vice President. pp. 1, 8; [Afro-American Cultural Center] Top achievers honored, p. 9. [Admissions, Office of, 1981] Twelve hundred accept admission.
- Tufts Observer, 1981 -- 1982; UP055.013; 1 Volumes
  This series consists of bound volumes of the Tufts Observer newspaper, dated from September 4, 1981 to May 7, 1982. In 1969, the Observer replaced the Tufts Weekly as the weekly student-published paper. Observer states that its objective is to be 'the newspaper of record' for Tufts University. The Observer covers current events and university news and sports. Typical features include editorials and opinion pieces, a calendar of events, art and culture articles, creative works, and comics.
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-09-04; UP055.013.013.00001 (Box 13)
    [Accounting Department] Senate not informed of new balance requirements. p. 3; [Administration] Sol Gittleman appointed new Provost; Steven Manos appointed new executive Vice President. p. 5.; Editorial re: new administrators. p. 12.; Levy, Robert I., research star joins Tufts (photo). p. 5.
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-09-11; UP055.013.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-09-18; UP055.013.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-09-25; UP055.013.013.00004 (Box 13)
    [Accreditation] Steering committee lists goals (photos) p. 3
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-10-02; UP055.013.013.00005 (Box 13)
    [Alumni council] Curriculum for alumni
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-10-09; UP055.013.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-10-16; UP055.013.013.00007 (Box 13)
    [Administration] Intellectual leaders assemble (photo). p. 4; [American association of University professors] Computer firm analyzes faculty salaries
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-10-23; UP055.013.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-10-30; UP055.013.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-11-06; UP055.013.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-11-13; UP055.013.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-11-20; UP055.013.013.00012 (Box 13)
    [Afro-American Cultural Center] Letter explaining Afro-American protest, p. 16.
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-12-04; UP055.013.013.00013 (Box 13)
    [Afro-American Cultural Center] Afro-American House officers speak on racism, p. 15.
  - Tufts Observer, 1981-12-11; UP055.013.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-01-29; UP055.013.013.00015 (Box 13)
    [Administration] Solomon, Howard resigns as dean, Maxwell succeeds (photo). p. 3. [Alumni 1982] Mastrovita, Robert P. and Stepanian, Ira named Alumni Trustees, p.23.
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-02-05; UP055.013.013.00016 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-02-12; UP055.013.013.00017 (Box 13)
    Sam Adams. Ex-CIA (Central Intelligence Agency) staff member speaks on Vietnam (photo).
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-02-19; UP055.013.013.00018 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-02-26; UP055.013.013.00019 (Box 13)
    [Afro-American Society] Letter re: isolationism, p. 8, 10.
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-03-05; UP055.013.013.00020 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-03-12; UP055.013.013.00021 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-03-19; UP055.013.013.00022 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-03-24; UP055.013.013.00023 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-04-16; UP055.013.013.00024 (Box 13)
    [Admissions] Tufts to enroll 1275 new students. pp. 1, 25.
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-04-23; UP055.013.013.00025 (Box 13)
    Committee evaluates problem areas (photos) p. 5
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-04-30; UP055.013.013.00026 (Box 13)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-05-07; UP055.013.013.00027 (Box 13)
- Tufts Observer, 1982 -- 1983; UP055.014; 1 Volumes
  This series consists of bound volumes of the Tufts Observer newspaper, dated from September 3, 1982 to May 6, 1983. In 1969, the Observer replaced the Tufts Weekly as the weekly student-published paper. Observer states that its objective is to be 'the newspaper of record' for Tufts University. The Observer covers current events and university news and sports. Typical features include editorials and opinion pieces, a calendar of events, art and culture articles, creative works, and comics.
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-09-03; UP055.014.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-09-10; UP055.014.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-09-17; UP055.014.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-09-24; UP055.014.014.00004 (Box 14)
    [Academic Honesty] Plagiarism at Tufts pp. 1, 23; [Afro-American Society] Former representative encourages activism (photo), p.4.
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-10-01; UP055.014.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-10-08; UP055.014.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-10-16; UP055.014.014.00007 (Box 14)
    [Admissons, Office of 1982] Reports drop in applicants. Alcohol Task Force encourages restraint on drinking: taking responsibility.
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-10-22; UP055.014.014.00008 (Box 14)
    Alcohol Task Force publishes guide. [American association of University professors] Writes PTP plan, Editorial
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-10-29; UP055.014.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-11-05; UP055.014.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-11-12; UP055.014.014.00011 (Box 14)
    [Africa and the New World] Holds Cuban/Afro colloquium, p. 5.
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-11-19; UP055.014.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-12-03; UP055.014.014.00013 (Box 14)
    AIESEC [L'association Internationale des Etudiants en Sciences Economiques et commerciales] Evaluates its Assets, p 11
  - Tufts Observer, 1982-12-10; UP055.014.014.00014 (Box 14)
    [African Drum Ensemble] "Yeve" performed, p. 13; [American association of University professors] Editorial re: faculty salaries
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-01-28; UP055.014.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-02-04; UP055.014.014.00016 (Box 14)
    [Administration] Officials to discuss draft laws. pp. 1, 25.
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-02-11; UP055.014.014.00017 (Box 14)
    [Administration] Tufts to comply with financial aid/draft law. pp. 1, 25.; Snowstorm causes chaos. pp. 3, 25.
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-02-25; UP055.014.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-03-04; UP055.014.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-03-11; UP055.014.014.00020 (Box 14)
    Richard Abedon (A 1985) [Gail Ann Lowney (J 1984)]. Travelers aid Haitians (photos); [Academic Honesty] Paper sales (letter) p. 8
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-03-18; UP055.014.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-03-24; UP055.014.00027 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-04-08; UP055.014.014.00022 (Box 14)
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-04-15; UP055.014.014.00023 (Box 14)
    [Alumni Association] Senior awards presented; Academic Awards 1983. Senior awards presented. [Allocations Board (ALBO)] PIRG funded via ALBO.
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-04-22; UP055.014.014.00024 (Box 14)
    [Academic Honesty] Senate discusses reinstatement of honor code p. 5
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-04-29; UP055.014.014.00025 (Box 14)
    [Admissons, Office of 1983] Admissions process remains complicated.
  - Tufts Observer, 1983-05-06; UP055.014.014.00026 (Box 14)
- Tufts Observer, 1983 -- 1984; UP055.015; 1 Volumes